fuelly.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy

_Last Updated – July 26, 2016_

Fuelly provides its users with automotive tracking services, via the Fuelly website and domain name offered from time to time, including those websites and domain names [related to Gas Cubby, Gas Tracker and aCar] (collectively, the “Website”) and/or the Fuelly mobile application, including the mobile applications Gas Cubby, Gas Tracker and aCar (collectively, the “Application” and together with the Website, the “Fuelly Service”). The Fuelly Service is owned and operated by Fuelly, LLC, a Texas limited liability company (“Fuelly”, “we” or “us”).

Your use of the Fuelly Service is subject to the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”).

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE FUELLY SERVICE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR TERMS OF SERVICE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO SUCH TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE FUELLY SERVICE.**

We are committed to respect and protect the privacy of the personal information we obtain from you through the Fuelly Service and we have created this Privacy Policy to inform you about how we collect, use and share your personal information, and about our privacy practices in general.

We are always ready to address your questions and concerns regarding this policy and our privacy practices. If you would like to contact customer service, please contact us via www.fuelly.com.

We continually strive to find new ways to enhance your experience with the Fuelly Service and we may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our privacy practices. You are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy periodically and to check the “Last Updated” date at the top of the Privacy Policy for the most recent version. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of notice through the Website, the Application, or any other part of the Fuelly Service.

  1. **Terms of Service.** Use of the Fuelly Service is subject to the terms of our Terms of Service found at www.fuelly.com/privacy, which is hereby incorporated and made part of this Privacy Policy. By using the Fuelly Service, you agree to be bound by our Terms of Service.
  2. **Types and Uses of Collected Information.** Fuelly collects two types of information about you: 
    1. **Personally Identifiable Information.** Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies a specific person. When you engage in certain activities via the Fuelly Service, including but not limited to creating an account, sending feedback, or otherwise participating in the Fuelly Service (collectively, “Identification Activities”), we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. If you elect to engage in an Identification Activity, however, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information about yourself, such as your name, address (including zip code), email address and/or telephone number. When you enroll in the Fuelly Service, we may also ask you to provide us with additional information, such as credit card information. Depending on the Identification Activity, some of the information we ask you to provide may be identified as mandatory and some identified as voluntary. If you do not provide mandatory information for a particular Identification Activity, you will not be permitted to engage in that Identification Activity with the Fuelly Service. Depending on the Identification Activity, Fuelly may not re-ask you for Personally Identifiable Information if such are already stored with us.

When you use the Fuelly Service, we may use GPS technology (or other similar geolocation technology) to determine your current location in order to display a location map with relevant content or otherwise provide for the transmission of data, including such data for any required or optional features of the Fuelly Service. If you do not want us to use your location for the purposes set forth above, you should turn off the location services for the Fuelly Service located in your account settings or in your mobile phone settings and/or within the Fuelly Service, provided that this may make certain or all features of the Fuelly Service inoperable.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information to provide products and/or services to you, administer sweepstakes and contests, enhance the operation of the Fuelly Service, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze use of the Fuelly Service, improve the Fuelly Service, and tailor your experience with third parties as provided below in this Privacy Policy. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, resolve disputes, accomplish administrative tasks, contact you, enforce our agreements with you, including our Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities.

    2. **Non-Personally Identifiable Information.** Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that does not identify a specific person. This type of information may include things like the Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) of the website you visited before coming to the Fuelly Service or otherwise participating in the Fuelly Service, the URL of the website you visit after leaving the Fuelly Service, the type of browser you are using, your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, mobile carrier information, mobile device information, or general and/or aggregated location data that does constitute Personally Identifiable Information. We, and/or our authorized Third Party Service Providers, may automatically collect this information when you visit or use the Fuelly Service through the use of electronic tools like Cookies and Web beacons or Pixel tags, as described below in this Privacy Policy. Most of the other information we collect for mobile, such as your mobile device identification and mobile device type, the request type, your mobile carrier, your mobile carrier user identification, and the content of your request, does not by itself identify you to Fuelly, though it may be unique or consist of or contain information that you consider personal.

We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, administer the Fuelly Service, analyze trends, gather demographic information, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. We may also share this information with our authorized Third Party Service Providers to measure the overall effectiveness of our products and services.

  3. **Release of Personally Identifiable Information.** We will not sell or share your Personally Identifiable Information with other parties except as provided below:

    1. **Authorized Third Party Service Providers.** Fuelly may provide products and services through third parties. These “Third Party Service Providers” perform functions on our or your behalf. You or We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with such Third Party Service Providers to fulfill orders, move data in or out of the Fuelly Service, analyze data, operate the Fuelly Service, troubleshoot and provide customer service. We may also provide personal information to individuals and companies with whom we have business relationships and may share your information with Third Party Service Providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by such parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control.
    2. **Remarketing.** Remarketing is a way for us to connect with people, based upon your past interactions with the Fuelly Service. Third-party marketing vendors may be hired by Fuelly to perform remarketing services. As a result, third-party vendors, including Google, may show Fuelly ads on sites on the Internet. Third-party vendors may use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to the Fuelly Service. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.
    3. **Acquisition.** As with any other company, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including Personally Identifiable Information. However, Personally Identifiable Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy.
    4. As required by law. We reserve the right to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us, enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, Terms of Service or other agreements or protect the rights, property or safety of the Fuelly Service, users of the Fuelly Service or others.
  4. **Release of Non-Personally Identifiable Information.** We may disclose or share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Third Party Service Providers and the general public. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information (which does not include any Personally Identifiable Information) or use Third Party Service Providers to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our users to administer the Fuelly Service. We may also publish this aggregated information for promotional purposes. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by us.

We may use Third Party Service Providers to serve ads when you participate in the Fuelly Service. These companies may use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits and use of the Fuelly Service, and visits to other websites or locations in order to provide, through the use of network tags, advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

  5. **Updating Information.** If you are enrolled in the Fuelly Service, you may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information by logging into your account and accessing the www.fuelly.com/driver/[your username]. We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes, as out-of-date Personally Identifiable Information may negatively affect the quality of your Fuelly Service experience. 

  6. **Choices on Collection/Use of Information.** You can always choose not to provide certain information, although a certain level of information is required to engage and participate in the Fuelly Service. You cannot opt-out of Administrative Emails. “Administrative Emails” relate to your activity on the Fuelly Service, and include but are not limited to emails regarding your account, requests or inquiries, and purchases of products and services. If you do not want to receive promotional emails from us, you may elect to opt-out of receiving promotional emails at any time after registering by e-mailing us at support@fuelly.com or by hitting the “unsubscribe” button at the bottom of any of our e-mails. 

  7. **Security of Information.** You can access your Personally Identifiable Information via the Fuelly Service with your password and username. This password is encrypted. We advise against sharing your password with anyone. If you access your account via a third-party site or service, you may have additional or different sign-in protections via that third-party site or service. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password and/or other sign-in mechanism appropriately and limiting access to your computer, browser, or mobile device by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. In the event that we believe that the security of your information may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. In addition, your Personally Identifiable Information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to. We may encrypt certain sensitive information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your Personally Identifiable Information is safe as it is transmitted to us. However, no data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies that do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from or via the Fuelly Service, and we are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

  8. **Data Tracking**

    1. **Cookies.** To facilitate and customize your experience with the Fuelly Service, we may store cookies on your computer or other similar device through which you access the Fuelly Service. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer or other device for record-keeping purposes that contains information about you. We use cookies to save you time while using the Fuelly Service, remind us who you are, and track and target your interests in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies also allow us to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information from you, like which pages you visited, what links you clicked on, and how you used the Fuelly Service. We may use Third Party Service Providers to display advertisements on the Fuelly Service. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer or similar device. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by the Fuelly Service only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Third Party Service Provider. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, however you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline cookies. Please note that if you decline or delete these cookies, some parts of the Fuelly Service may not work properly.
    2. **Other Tracking Devices.** We may use other industry standard technologies like pixel tags and web beacons to track your use of the Fuelly Service, or we may allow our Third Party Service Providers to use these devices on our behalf. When you access the Fuelly Service or open or click an email, pixel tags and web beacons generate a Non-Personally Identifiable notice of that action. Pixel tags allow us to measure and improve our understanding of visitor traffic and behavior on the Fuelly Service, as well as give us a way to measure our promotions and performance. We may also utilize pixel tags and web beacons provided by our marketing partners for the same purposes.
  9. **Privacy Policies of Third Party Websites.** This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you via the Fuelly Service. Other websites or services that may be accessible through the Fuelly Service may have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you use, link or visit any such website, we urge you review the website’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

  10. **Privacy Settings.** As a user, you may have limited access to privacy settings. These settings help hide information you wish to share with other users and/or the public. It is up to you to select the appropriate privacy settings. If you don’t agree with the available privacy settings, please stop using the Fuelly Service.

  11. **Public Areas.** We may provide areas on the Fuelly Service where you can publicly post information about yourself or can communicate with others such as on forums. This information may be accessible by other users and companies and may appear on other websites or web searches, and therefore this information could be read, collected, and used by others. We have no control over who reads your postings or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so please use caution when posting any content or providing anything that could be deemed personal information.

  12. **Notice of Privacy Rights to California Residents.** California law requires that we provide you with a summary of your privacy rights under the California Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) and the California Business and Professions Code. As required by COPPA, we will provide you with the categories of Personally Identifiable Information that we collect through the Fuelly Service and the categories of third party persons or entities with whom such Personally Identifiable Information may be shared for direct marketing purposes at your request. California law requires us to inform you, at your request, (1) the categories of Personally Identifiable Information we collect and what third parties we share that information with; (2) the names and addresses of those third parties; and (3) examples of the products marketed by those companies. COPPA further requires us to allow you to control who you do not want us to share that information with. To obtain this information, please send a request by email or physical mail to the address found below. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Personally Identifiable Information you do not want us to share with our marketing partners. The request should be sent to the attention of our legal department, and labeled “California Customer Choice Notice.” Please allow 30 days for a response. Also, please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your Personally Identifiable Information or requesting this notice.

  13. **Children.** The Fuelly Service are not directed to people under the age of 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at www.fuelly.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account.

  14. **Customer Service.** For assistance or questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the Fuelly Service, you may contact us at www.fuelly.com.
